2021年7月
On July of 2021,
一位ID为BlueBlackJupiter的Reddit用户
a reddit user named BlueBlackJupiter
发布了一篇帖子，在社区里掀起轩然大波
would make a post that would send the community into a spiral,
标题仅为
titled simply,
《楼上邻居跟踪我》
Upstairs Neighbors Talks Me.
我甚至不知该从何说起，这情况实在太过离奇和恐怖
I can't even begin to describe how unbelievable and frightening the situation is.
故事始于2020年9月1日，我刚搬进新公寓后不久
It started shortly after I moved into my apartment on September 1st of 2020.
我的治疗师察觉到我坐立不安，便问我是否有安全感
My therapist picked up on the fact I seemed uneasy, then asked if I felt safe.
莫名其妙的是，我楼上的邻居
Unexplicably, my neighbor above
会跟着我从一个房间到另一个房间，就像在我头顶盘旋
would follow me from room to room and hover over me.
比如说，如果我在卧室，她就已经在我头顶正上方的房间里了
For example, if I'm in my bedroom, she will already be in the room above it.
如果我起身去厨房，她几秒钟后就会尾随而至
If I get up and go to my kitchen, she will tail behind seconds later.
如果我回房间，她也会照做，有时还会重重地跺脚
If I go back to my room, she will do the same, sometimes stomping.
她简直就是我的影子
She's literally my shadow.
头几个月，几乎我每次起身做点什么，她都会这样
For the first few months, she did this nearly every single time I got up to do something.
即使是在洗澡或上厕所这种更私密的时刻
Even during more intimate moments, like taking a shower or using the bathroom.
她接着解释
She would go on to explain
自己如何排除了所有巧合，甚至接受了心理评估
how she ruled out any coincidences and even underwent a psychological evaluation,
评估证实她并未出现任何妄想症状
which confirmed that she wasn't experiencing any delusions.
她怀疑有隐藏摄像头
She suspected hidden cameras,
并指出即使她没发出任何声音，邻居似乎也能对她的行为作出反应
noting the neighbor seemed to react to things she was doing, even if it made no noise.
房东声称维修人员从未进入过那套公寓
The landlord claimed maintenance had never accessed a unit
而且那里住着两个人，尽管其中一个已经悄悄搬走了
and that two people lived there, though one had secretly moved out.
她强调这并非隔音效果差，因为她从其他邻居那里什么也听不到
She emphasized it wasn't poor insulation, as she heard nothing from the other neighbors.
唯一能听见的只有那个女人的沉重脚步声
Only the woman's heavy stomping,
她的烟雾报警器
her smoke alarm,
和她的洗澡声
and her showers.
为了证明自己的说法，她很快上传了视频证据来佐证这一奇怪现象
To help her case, she would soon upload video proof of this strange phenomenon.
那是一段九分半钟的视频，她在公寓里从一个房间走到另一个房间
A nine and a half minute video in which she moves around the apartment, from room to room.
虽然很难听得一清二楚
And while it's hard to make things out perfectly,
但确实听起来像是有人在她头顶上走动
it does sound like someone is walking around above her.
但正如她所说，是否真的在模仿她的动作，这点无法完全确定
Whether or not they were shadowing her movements, though, like she said, that can't be made out fully.
后来有一天，毫无征兆地
Then one day, out of the blue,
她发现门垫上放了一瓶漂白剂
she would find a bottle of bleach left on her doormat,
她认为这可能是一种威胁
which she saw as a possible threat.
除了视频，楼主还声称她的朋友留宿时也目睹了这一切
Other than the video, OP would also claim that her friend has also witnessed this while staying over.
我朋友从今天早上起就在我家工作
My friend had been working at my place since this morning.
我大部分时间都待在卧室里，而她一直在另一个房间用她的电脑
I've largely stayed in my bedroom, while she has been in another room at her computer.
我们注意到了以下情况
We've noticed the following.
早上我朋友设置电脑时，我的邻居在我们头顶上停留了片刻然后走开了
When my friend was setting up her computer in the morning, my neighbor came above us briefly before walking away.
我离开公寓一个多小时
When I left my apartment for a little over an hour,
朋友说邻居来到她头顶上，跺了一会儿脚，然后大部分时间都保持安静
my friend said she came above her, stomping for a bit, then stayed mostly silent.
她没有跟着我朋友走动
She didn't follow my friend around,
但我朋友说她基本都待在办公桌前，没怎么走动
but my friend said she was mostly at her desk and didn't really walk around.
我回到公寓后，去洗了个澡
When I returned to my apartment, I took a shower.
我和朋友都听到楼上邻居在我浴室附近，在我洗澡期间，她不时地跺着脚
My friend and I heard my neighbor above, near my bathroom, as she stomped periodically throughout my shower.
我打这行字的时候，她就在我卧室的正上方
She's above me in my bedroom as I type this.
前方广告，请空降5:48
每当生活变得忙碌，我们就很容易把健康抛诸脑后
Whenever life gets busy, it's so easy to push our health to the side.
即使感觉有些不对劲，我也会告诉自己以后再处理
Even when something feels off, I tell myself I'll deal with it later.
而那个“以后”通常永远不会到来
And later usually never comes.
老实说，光是找个医生就感觉像是一场磨难
And honestly, just finding a doctor can feel like a whole ordeal.
在打电话给诊所
Between calling offices,
弄清楚谁有空
figuring out who's available,
以及查询谁还在接收新病人之间，我通常只会一拖再拖，直到非去不可
and checking who's even taking new patients, I usually just end up pushing it off until I absolutely have to go.
这件事给我带来了巨大的恐惧，并加剧了我的健康问题
This has caused me a significant amount of fear, and exacerbated my medical issues.
我好几个月没法工作，租期里有近四分之一的时间都住在朋友家
I've lost months of work, and have spent nearly a quarter of my lease living with friends.
我活在极度的恐惧中
I live very much in fear
担心这个人可能会伤害我，因为她全天候24小时都死死地盯着我
this person could harm me as they are fixated on me 24-7,
而且从不离开她的公寓
and never ever leave their apartment.
这情况也太诡异了
This is an extremely strange situation,
鉴于我身边人的行为举止，我相信有人知道些什么
and given how folks in my periphery have behaved, I believe someone knows something.
我不能再对此保持沉默了
I can't keep quiet about this any longer,
因为我担心她会把同样的事情做到别人身上
in fear she might do this to someone else.
起初，这个帖子遭到了排山倒海般的质疑
Now, initially this post would be met with a wave of doubt.
倒可以理解，毕竟认为自己被邻居跟踪是妄想症或偏执狂最常见的症状之一
Understandably, thinking that one is being stalked by their neighbor is one of the most common signs of delusion or paranoia.
但也有人没有直接否定她
But others didn't dismiss her outright,
因为她看起来很理性，也清楚这一切听起来有多么难以置信
as she seemed rational and aware of how implausible it all sounded.
她甚至去做了精神健康评估
Even going as far as to have her mental health evaluated,
还请了朋友和她同住，以确认她听到的声音
and having a friend stay with her and confirm what she was hearing.
不过，主要问题依然无法忽视
Though the main question stood,
如果邻居真的在做这件事
if the neighbor was indeed doing this,
她是如何全天候都确切知道楼主位置的呢
how would they know exactly where she was at any point during the day and night?
比较主流的理论是，她的住处可能被安装了窃听器
Some of the main theories that would be brought up were that her place was possibly bugged,
布满了用于追踪她行踪的隐藏设备
wired up with hidden devices to track her movements.
为了证明自己并非凭空想象
Determined to prove she wasn't imagining this,
她开始把自己的公寓翻了个底朝天
she began tearing her apartment apart.
然而，一个周末的时间，她和一位朋友搜遍了每一寸角落
However, over a weekend, her and a friend would search every inch,
拆下灯具，检查通风口
removing light fixtures, checking vents,
插座、烟雾报警器，甚至墙上微小的孔洞和裂缝
outlets, smoke alarms, even tiny holes and crevices in the walls.
她们关掉了所有灯，用手机摄像头在黑暗中扫描红外线闪光
They turned off all the lights and scanned the dark for infrared glints with their phone cameras.
结果一无所获
But absolutely nothing came out.
没有任何证据表明她的住处被窃听，或者有人想要加害于她
No evidence that her place was bugged, or that someone was out to get her.
只有头顶上那如影随形的脚步声，模仿着她的一举一动
Only the same footsteps above her, mirroring her every movement.
她的最后一次更新是在2021年7月11日
Her last update came on July 11th of 2021.
在经过数日的搜寻、记录
After days of searching, of documenting,
以及尝试了网上陌生人能建议的各种测试之后
of trying every test strangers on the internet could suggest.
她承认自己仍然一无所获
She admitted that she still hadn't been able to find anything,
并且仍然不确定该如何看待整件事
and that she still wasn't sure what to make of the whole thing.
她感谢了所有人的帮助，并说如果有任何重大进展，她会发布新帖
She thanked everyone for their help, and said if anything major happened, she would make a new post.
她再也没有发过
She never did.
可悲的是，像这样的故事并不少见
Stories like this, sadly, aren't rare.
其实有些社区就是围绕着那些坚信自己正被跟踪的人们建立起来的
In fact, there are entire online communities built around people who have convinced themselves that they are actively being stalked.
大多数时候，这些所谓的规律在仔细审视下都会不攻自破
Most of the time, the patterns fall apart under scrutiny.
但这一次感觉有所不同
But this one felt different.
有了视频，有了那瓶被留在她门口的奇怪漂白剂
With the video, the strange bottle of bleach left at her doorstep,
还有那位留宿并证实了这一切的朋友
and the friend who stayed over and confirmed it.
我内心有部分想把这归结为纯粹的偏执
Part of me wants to dismiss it as just paranoia.
但是…
But...
我说不准
I don't know.
你怎么看呢
What do you think?
Toy739
这是油管上的一个“异类”
Is a YouTube Anomaly.
频道创建于2007年，乍一看
Created in 2007, Toy739 is a YouTube channel, that at first,
这频道不过是某个人的私人视频档案馆
seems like nothing more than someone's personal video archive.
这个频道似乎由一位狗仔队或某摄像师运营
The channel appears to be operated by a paparazzi, or some sort of videographer.
里面全是商场秀、名人露面、采访和产品发布的片段
Filled with clips from mall shows, celebrity appearances, interviews, and product launches.
所有视频都很短，通常只有15到30秒
All of them are short, usually 15-30 seconds,
而且都没有标题，直接用相机的默认文件名上传
and all of them are left untitled, uploaded with their default camera file names.
没有视频简介，没有封面，没有剪辑，也无意吸引任何关注
There are no video descriptions, no thumbnails, no editing, and no attempt to draw attention.
表面上看，这个人似乎是把这个频道当作某种工作档案或云存储来使用
Seemingly, this person is using this channel as some sort of work archive or cloud storage.
该频道存续时间很长，从 2012 年至 2019 年间累计上传了逾 7500 个视频
And despite its longevity on over 7.5 thousand videos uploaded from 2012 to 2019.
但它几乎完全不为人知
It has remained almost completely under the radar.
大部分视频的观看次数都是零
With most of its videos having zero views.
真相是，这个频道隐藏着一个黑暗的秘密
But the truth is, this channel hides a dark secret.
当你开始向深处滚动，你可能会开始注意到一些端倪
As you begin to scroll deep enough, you might begin to notice something.
一个男人开始越来越频繁地出现
A pattern of a man who begins appearing more and more
并成为这些视频的唯一焦点，这是一个规律
as the sole focus of these videos.
表面上，Toy739不过是某个人的工作档案
On a surface, Toy739 is nothing more than someone's work archive.
但在表象之下，它是有史以来持续时间最长的跟踪影像档案之一
But beneath the surface, it's one of the longest running stalking archives ever recorded.
数千个关于同一个男人的视频，跨越了整整八年的时间
With thousands of videos of the same man, taken across a span of 8 entire years.
拍摄自多个地点
From multiple locations.
所有这一切，都被上传到了这里
All of it, uploaded right here.
而这一切，他本人完全不知情
And all of it, completely without his knowledge.
起初，这种对这个人的奇怪迷恋——
At first, it seems like this strange fixation with this person,
我们称他为“摄影师”
we'll call him the cameraman.
似乎是在整个频道的生命周期中逐渐形成的
Had developed gradually throughout the entire life of the channel.
早期的视频更专注于他的本职工作
With the earlier videos being more focused on their actual work.
拍摄名人与各类活动
Of shooting clips of celebrities and events.
但经过深入分析，这位神秘人物似乎从频道创建之初就已经登场
But on deeper analysis, it appears that this enigmatic figure has made his appearance since the very inception of the channel.
在2011年6月3日上传的第三个视频中
On the third video ever uploaded, on the 3rd of June 2011,
我们的摄影师在人群中首次亮相
our cameraman makes his first appearance within the crowd.
然而仅仅一个月后，7月23日，我们又看到了一个完全以他为主角的视频
Only a month later though, on July 23rd, we get another video fully dedicated to him.
之后是11月
Then another in November.
之后还有
Then another.
如此种种
And another.
不胜枚举
从这时起，这类视频变得愈发频繁，同时仍然维持着频道的主要用途
From this point on, they become much more frequent, while still maintaining the main purpose of the channel.
最终，他在岁月流转中的反复出现
And eventually, his repeated presence across the years
使他比那些模特、歌手或路人都要显眼得多
makes him stand out much more than the models, the singers or the random crowds.
他成了主角，成了焦点
He becomes the main focus, the focal point.
从阳台、楼梯间、栏杆后、以及房间的另一头追踪拍摄他
Following him from balconies, stairwells, from behind rails, and across rooms.
一段时间后，他们甚至开始在他工作之外拍摄他
After some time, they began even filming him outside of his work.
他们拍摄他休息时、
They filmed him while on break,
与人交谈时、
while engaging in conversation,
乘电梯时、
while using the elevator,
以及在手机上发信息时的样子
while messaging on his phone.
这位摄影师从一开始就在
The cameraman was there from the very start.
但这种痴迷的焦点慢慢收紧，直到他成为整个主题
But the obsession slowly tightens its focus until he becomes the entire subject.
那么现在问题来了
So now the question stands.
这个男人是谁
Who is this man?
为什么会发生这种事
Why is this happening?
更重要的是，镜头后面的人是谁
And more importantly, who's behind our camera?
该频道似乎还上传了一些短视频
The channel also seems to have a few shorts uploaded.
其中两个似乎是关于他的
Two of which seem to be about him.
一个在2014年，拍摄者从坐着的他身旁走过，并拍下了他
One in 2014, in which our person films him as they walk past him sitting down.
另一个在2019年，似乎就在他旁边
And another one in 2019, where they seem to be right next to him.
我发现有趣的是，与长视频不同，这些短视频是有标题的
What I found interesting here, is that unlike the videos, these shorts are titled.
第一个标题是ON9
The first one is titled ON9.
这是香港的粤语网络俚语，意思是“超级白痴”或“蠢货”
Which is a Cantonese internet slang in Hong Kong, which stands for Fucking idiot, or dumbass.
即粤语“戇鳩”
而第二个翻译过来是“混账东西”或“一群禽兽”
While the second translates to effing animal, or bunch of animals.
仅此一点，就彻底改变了整个事件的性质
This one thing, changes the dynamic completely.
坦白说，这让整个情况比原先更加黑暗
And frankly, makes this whole situation, much darker than it already was.
因为这种跟踪，从来不是出于迷恋，或浪漫的痴狂
Because this stalking, was never coming from a place of fascination, or romantic obsession.
而是源于绝对的憎恨
But of absolute hate.
这是一种静默的、沸腾的恨意，在近十年的时间里被秘密地拍摄下来
A quiet, seething hate, filmed in secret, for nearly a decade.
Toy739背后的确切目的从未得到证实
The exact purpose behind Toy739 has never been confirmed.
但有些线索能让我们对这里发生的事情有个大概的了解
But there are some clues that would give us an idea on what's going on here.
首先是地点
First of all, the location.
大部分镜头都是在香港拍摄的
Most of the footage was filmed in Hong Kong.
地点常常是钻石山的荷里活广场
Often, at the Plaza Hollywood Mall in Diamond Hill.
这是一个以举办小型音乐会、时装秀和品牌活动而闻名的热门商场
A popular mall known for housing small concerts, fashion shows, and brand events.
这就解释了背景中源源不断的模特、歌手和名人
This explains the constant stream of models, singers, and celebrities in the background.
在香港，这些活动常常吸引大批自由摄影师
In Hong Kong, these events often draw crowds of freelance photographers.
他们也被称为“龙友”大叔
Also known as event uncles.
他们整日记录着公共演出
Who spend their days documenting public shows.
或为工作，或为爱好
Either for work, or as a hobby.
但时至今日，没人知道那位摄影师是谁
But to this day, nobody knows who the camera man is.
也没人知道是谁在拍他
And nobody knows who filmed him.
没人知道此人为何花了近十年时间秘密录制他
Nobody knows why they spent nearly a decade secretly recording him.
整理了数千个片段，并将它们全部上传到这里
Compiling thousands of clips, and uploading them all on here.
这会是某种单方面的敌对吗
Could it be some sort of one-way rivalry?
或许是偏执
Maybe paranoia?
或是由某种妄想驱动的痴迷
Or obsession driven by some delusion?
也许整个主页就是对此的记录
Maybe the whole page is a documentation of that.
记录了一个人失去理智，一步步坠入精神疾病深渊的过程
Of a person losing their senses, and falling deeper and deeper into mental illness.
而在翻阅了经年累月的影像资料后
And while scouring through the years and years of footage.
有几个罕见的瞬间让我印象深刻
There were a handful of rare moments that stood out to me.
在那些瞬间，那个几乎从不看镜头的男人，似乎注意到了镜头
Moments where the man who almost never looks at the camera seems to notice it.
之后，在2019年12月5日上传的最后一段视频中
Then on the last video ever uploaded on December 5th, 2019,
我们的摄影师环顾四周
our cameraman takes a look around,
凝视了对着他的摄像机一秒钟
spots the camera aimed at him for a second,
然后走开了
and then walks away.
有种感觉告诉我，根据最后一个视频
Something tells me that based on that last video
以及之后上传的戛然而止
and the complete abrupt stop to the uploads after this,
也许他最终认出了那个跟踪他多年的人
maybe he did eventually recognize the person who had been following him for all those years.
或许最后那一眼直视镜头并非偶然
Maybe that last direct look into the camera wasn't an accident.
或许他终于看清了跟踪者的面目
Maybe he finally saw a stalker
并选择亲手了结这一切
and chose to put an end to it himself.
2024年6月16日，在Reddit的r/rbi子版块上
On June 16th, 2024, on the r/rbi subreddit,
出现了一个帖子，标题是《有没有一个叫莎拉的女孩失踪了》
a post would be made titled, Is there a Sarah missing?
是这样，我非常犹豫要不要发这个帖子
So, I'm very hesitant to post this
因为我不想让我朋友因为和我分享这些信息而在工作上惹麻烦
because I don't want my friend to get in trouble at work for sharing this info with me.
事情是这样的，我朋友大约一周前在工作中收到了一封信和两张照片
Here's the deal, my friend received a letter with two photos at work about a week ago.
可以说有点诡异，给人一种连环杀手的感觉
It is, at minimum, very creepy and gives off serial killer vibes.
他们已经通过公司的安保系统以及当地警察局和其他机构上报了此事
They have already reported it off the corporation's security chain and local police department, as well as other agencies.
但显然当地警方似乎并不重视
But apparently the local police don't seem to take it seriously,
他们告诉朋友只需把信的数码照片发给他们
and they told them to just send them digital photos of the letter
然后把实物扔掉得了，因为信件经过邮政系统，不会有什么用处
and then trash the real material because it went through the mail and would not be useful.
所以我求他给了我一份副本
So, I begged for a copy,
心想，如果有人能解开这个谜团，那一定是RBI的网友们了
and thought, if anyone can solve this mystery, it's RBI.
楼主发来了这封信及其内容物的照片
OP would send photos of this letter and what was inside it.
信封上没有回信地址
The envelope had no return address on it,
只有一个来自佐治亚州亚特兰大的邮戳，和写着的“塔吉特公司”
only a postmark from Atlanta, Georgia, and Target Corporation written on it.
信封里有一张纸和两张照片
Inside this envelope was a single sheet of paper, paper, and two photos.
纸上写着
The paper read.
塔吉特百货商店销售许多高品质产品
Target department stores sell many high quality products.
速比涛回旋镖游泳镜，即使一位年轻女士
The speedo boomerang swim goggles that will securely strap around a person's head,
在峡谷中奋力划皮划艇时，也能牢固地绑在头上
even when a young woman is vigorously paddling a kayak through a canyon.
还有，冷藏柜里出售的美味瓶装激浪汽水
Also, delicious bottles of Mountain Dew that are sold in the refrigerated coolers.
一位年轻女士，莎拉，正在哈瓦西河上奋力地划着皮划艇
A young woman, Sarah, is vigorously paddling a kayak down the Hiwassee River.
至于照片
As for the photographs,
其中一张是护目镜的照片
one of them is a picture of goggles,
与之前提到的速比涛回旋镖护目镜一模一样
exactly the same speedo boomerang goggles mentioned before.
第二张照片是在一个车展上的一辆红色丰田Matrix
And a second photo is of a red Toyota Matrix at an auto show.
这封信本身，至少可以说是光怪陆离
The letter itself is bizarre, to say the least.
它用完美工整的笔迹书写，但描述的内容却毫无逻辑
It's written in perfect uniform handwriting, but what it's describing makes no sense.
信的内容从赞美塔吉特商店产品优质
It goes from praising Target stores for their high quality products,
跳跃到古怪地描述一位名叫莎拉的女子
to oddly describing a woman named Sarah,
说她显然正在奋力地沿着哈瓦西河划皮划艇
who's apparently vigorously paddling a kayak down the Hiwassee River.
描述得异常具体
It's strangely specific.
很快，网络侦探们发现这并非孤立事件
Soon, internet investigators would discover that this isn't an isolated incident,
因为找到了多个同样在塔吉特工作的人发的多个帖子
as multiple posts from multiple people who also work at Target
讨论在他们的信箱里发现的类似信件
would be found discussing similar letters found in their PO box.
准确地说是另外四封信，始于2023年，一直持续到2025年
Four extra letters precisely, beginning in 2023 and continuing into 2025.
每一封都以同样赞美塔吉特产品开头
Each one starts with the same praise of Target product,
并描述一位具名的单身女子
and describes a lone woman by name,
她总是在某条特定的河流或湖泊中奋力地划着皮划艇
who's always vigorously paddling a kayak in a specific river or lake.
有在哈瓦西河的莎拉
There was Sarah in Hiwassee River,
斯科科米什河的艾弗里
Avery in Skokomish River,
又一个在萨斯奎哈纳河的莎拉
a Sarah again in Sesquahanna River,
卡贝托加马湖的阿什利
an Ashley in Kabetagama Lake,
以及在塔克西吉河的斯蒂芬妮
and a Stephanie in Tuckaseggee River.
这封信，显然是年代最久远的一封，其格式与其他信件有所不同
This letter, which is apparently the oldest one, deviates in the format from the rest.
首先，这封信没有附上那张红色汽车的照片
First of all, this one doesn't have the picture of the red car included.
取而代之的是一张百货商店里穿着比基尼的人体模型的照片
Instead, it has a picture of a mannequin wearing a bikini in a department store.
一辆废弃的冰淇淋车
An abandoned ice cream truck,
1974年款AM General FJ-8A
a 1974 AM General FJ-8A,
停在一片广阔、偏远、贫瘠的沙质沙漠中的一个废车场里
parked in a junkyard in a vast remote barren sandy desert.
又一个异常具体的细节，给出了确切的型号、制造商和地点
Another oddly specific detail, giving the exact model, make and location.
搜索这个描述会找到一辆停在加利福尼亚
Googling that description pulls up the exact same truck model
一个废车场里的完全相同的卡车型号
that's sitting in a junkyard in California.
但更奇怪的是，如果我们开始搜索信中这些名字
But what's even stranger, is what happens if we start searching the names in these letters,
以及河流和湖泊所在的州
alongside the states where the rivers and lakes are located.
我至少能找到四名受害者，她们与信中提到的名字和地点能轻易地对应上
I was able to find at least four victims that easily line up with the names and the locations brought up within these letters.
哈瓦西河在田纳西州，与之可能匹配的莎拉
A possible match for the Sarah at the Hiwassee River, which is in Tennessee,
是莎拉·米歇尔·菲利普斯，22岁，来自田纳西州米兰市
is a Sarah Michelle Phillips, who was 22, from Milan, Tennessee.
她于2019年1月失踪
She disappeared in January of 2019.
同年10月，她的遗骸在一片林区被发现
Her remains were found in October of that same year in a wooded area.
另一位在萨斯奎哈纳河的莎拉，该河位于宾夕法尼亚州
A match for the other Sarah in Susquehanna River, which is in Pennsylvania,
与之匹配的是14岁的莎拉·雷·博斯，来自宾夕法尼亚州罗切斯特镇
is a Sarah Rae Boehm, age 14, from Rochester Township in Pennsylvania,
她于1994年7月失踪，同年11月被发现死亡
who went missing in July of 1994, and was found deceased in November of that same year.
她的遗骸在俄亥俄州柏林中心的柏林水库被发现，距离她家60英里
Her remains were found at the Berlin Reservoir in Berlin Center, Ohio, 60 miles from her home.
在卡贝托加马湖的阿什利，该湖位于明尼苏达州
A possible match for the Ashley at the Kabetagama Lake, which is in Minnesota,
与之可能匹配的是33岁的阿什利·林恩·卡尔森
is an Ashley Lynn Carlson, age 33,
来自明尼苏达州派恩县，她于2021年9月失踪，同年11月被发现死亡
from Pine County, Minnesota, who went missing in September of 2021, and was found deceased in November of that same year.
经过两个月的搜寻
After two months of searching,
她的遗骸在加利福尼亚州丽娜湖附近的米拉克印第安保留地被发现
her remains were found near Lake Lena, California, on the Mia Lax Band Reservation.
而在塔克西吉河的斯蒂芬妮，该河位于北卡罗来纳州
And Stephanie, of Tuckaseggee River, which is in North Carolina,
可以与来自北卡罗来纳州兰伯顿的斯蒂芬妮·林恩·刘易斯相匹配
can be matched with Stephanie Lynn Lewis, from Lumberton, North Carolina,
她于2004年10月失踪，至今仍下落不明
who went missing in October of 2004, and remains still missing till this day.
最后一次被人看到，是她试图搭便车去弗吉尼亚
Last seen, trying to hitch a ride to Virginia.
更离奇的是，这四起案件，至今仍未侦破
What's even stranger, is that all four of these cases, still remain unsolved, till this day.
这意味着，幕后黑手可能仍逍遥法外
Meaning, whoever is behind them, could still be out there.
尽管这些信令人发毛，但当局大多对此漠不关心
Despite how unsettling they are, the letters have been mostly met with indifference from the authorities.
无论幕后是谁，他仍在向全国各地的塔吉特商店邮寄这些信件
Whoever is behind them, is still out there mailing them to targets all over the country.
一些人推测，这不过是某种妄想或心理上的固着
Some have theorized that this is nothing more than some sort of delusional or psychological fixation.
这至少可以解释那些胡言乱语的文字，以及寄出的信件数量之多
This would at least explain the nonsensical writing, and the amount of them sent out.
而另一些人则认为，这些信是真切的忏悔录
While others believe that these letters are actual confessions,
是某个悬而未决的恐怖事件留下的线索，或蛛丝马迹
sent in as clues, or as breadcrumbs, of someone's horrors that were never solved.
但在我们掌握确凿证据之前
But until we have some concrete evidence,
塔吉特信件之谜，仍然只是网络上众多离奇难解的怪事之一
the target letter's mystery, remains as just another one of the many odd inexplicable oddities of the internet.
话说到此，我就不多言了
And with that being said, I will leave it at that.
希望您在此逗留愉快
I hope you've enjoyed your stay.
咱们不久后再见
And I will see you, very soon.